Alphabetical Pamphlet Collection
University of Notre Dame Archives
- Alphabetical Pamphlet Collection: Printed Material, PALP
  - Peace Education in the Curriculum of the Schools / by Wolfe, John M., STD and Peace Education Committee, 1934; PALP 11/53
  - The Temporal Power / by Wood, L. J. S., 1919; PALP 11/54
  - Are Anglican Ministers Catholic Priests? / by Woodlock, Francis SJ, c1929; PALP 11/55
  - Lourdes and Modern Miracles / by Woodlock, Francis SJ, PALP 11/56
  - First Assemble of the World Council of Churches - Findings and Decisions / by World Council of Churches, 1948; PALP 11/57
  - Worship v. XXXVI:II / by Liturgical Press, Collegeville, St. John's Abbey, 1962/01; PALP 11/58
  - Studying Effectively / by Wrenn, C. Gilbert and Robert P. Larsen, 1954; PALP 11/59
  - The Role of the Catholic American in Internation Peace / by Wright, Herbert, 1937; PALP 11/60
  - Seven Sins are Deadly / by Wrzaszczak, Chester JCD, 1961; PALP 11/61
  - The Guardian of Liberty / by Wynne, John J. SJ, 1917; PALP 11/62; Subject: Church and Liberty
  - Youth Leaders Digest v. XI No. 7, 1949/04; PALP 11/63
  - What is "Benediction" ? / by De Zulueta, F. M. SJ, PALP 11/64
  - Tre-Ore for Congregational Use / by Ziebarth, Joseph A., Rev, 1938; PALP 11/65